<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<mission id="HackerWar_CTF_01" activeCheck="true" shouldIgnoreSenderVerification="false">
  <goals>
    <!-- Goals here -->
    <goal type="getstring" target="p4tch_sund14l_w1r3d_h4ndsh4k3" />
  </goals>
  <!-- 
  Add your mission start and end items here
  missionStart val="0">loadConditionalActions:Actions/TestActions.xml</missionStart>
  missionEnd val="1">addRank</missionEnd> 
  -->
  <missionStart>loadConditionalActions:Actions/BattleActions/Start_ctfMain01.xml</missionStart>
  <missionEnd val="1">addRankSilent</missionEnd>
  <nextMission>Missions/AssistantMissions/Assistant_08.xml</nextMission>
  <!-- 
  <posting title="startingMission">This would be the post on a message board if it was on them.</posting>
  -->
  
  <posting title="Hacker Wars Team CTF">
Welcome back to Hacker Wars! Now that our teams have been set out;
 It's time for our first Team battle. Unlike the previous solo
 matches, where our hackers battled it out one on one, this time
 it's going to be more of a race for each team member. It will be
 a strong test of each team's ability to be observent more than
 anything else.
 
Both teams have approximately five minutes to piece together
the correct password and reply to the mission email with it.
 
Let's see how each of our teams do in this much more complex test
 of skill:
 
     Naix's Team        vs.      #PLAYERNAME#'s Team

	
Please note that this mission may take a long time. For the time
 this mission takes, you will not be able to access any other 
 missions or contracts! Keep this in mind before accepting.
</posting>
  
  <email>
    <sender>Battleboard Bot</sender>
    <subject>Capture the Flag Event Started</subject>
    <body>#PLAYERNAME#,

This email is to inform you that you have started a capture the flag
event against Naix. If this was not you, we recommend restarting
your computer immediately!

Sadly, we're having issues with Team services at the moment, so
 this mission is just going to be a face-off between you and Naix!

To find out how Capture The Flag works, hit up the 'ReadMe.txt' on
 the CTF start point.
 
 Otherwise, the event has started! You will find the IP
 to your CTF start point below.
 
 Good luck!
 Get going!
 
 - Hacker_Wars Battleboard Bot</body>
    <attachments>
      <!-- Add attachments like links and notes here -->
	  <note title="Main Goals">You need to piece together a final password to reply to the mission email with.
1) Connect to the Start Point, read through the ReadMe.txt
2) Once familiar, use the hints and scanning tools to identify your next computer.
3) As you go through take note of the passwords you uncover and the order in which you find them, you may need them later on.
4) Use found passwords to decrypt more information and identify the next set of passwords.
IMPORTANT! Pay attention to the hints in text files. They may help you.</note>
	  <link comp="ctfMain01" />
    </attachments>
  </email>
</mission>