<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8" ?>
<Computer id="ctfMain01"
	name="Hacker Wars CTF StartPoint"
	ip="160.8.195.15"
	allowsDefaultBootModule="false"
	type="empty">

  <portsForCrack val="2" />
  <ports>21, 25</ports>
  <trace time="-1" />
  
  <adminPass pass="c4pture_th3_fl4g" />
  
  <file path="home/Themes" name="ThemeChanger.exe">#THEMECHANGER_EXE#</file>
 
  <file path="home" name="Instructions.txt"> --- Capture The Flag Instructions ---

  - Each team is give a set of 3 passwords. Onle one of
   these passwords will open the encrypted file.
   
  - Once each encrypted file has been opened another 3 passwords will be generated;
   these will open the next encrypted file.
  
  - This will happen 3 times until the player is left with 4 seperate passwords.
  
  - To win the challenge the team must then enter all the passwords together in
   reply to the mission email, however this may use different passwords altogether
   (the final encrypted file will display instructions on this)
  
  - Your teammates will periodically help you out by sending messages through (Terminal / MsgBoard)
</file>
  <file path="home" name="ReadMe.txt">Welcome to the Capture the Flag server!
This is the first server you will start your journey on. Capture the Flag is
largely a gamemode about guessing and speed, but also it is a test of how 
observent team members can be. As you proceed through each server you
will find an encrypted file on each. The servers in question will each
contain a password to unlock another encrypted file, until finally one team
or the other team finds the final encrypted file providing them with details
on a special string they must then reply to the original email with.

It is strongly advised that teams take notes about each password they find,
as they may prove very useful later on...

You will find your first encrypted file at the connected nodes:

Your first set of Passwords for the encrypted file are:
  (without the quotation marks)
    - "midn1gh7"
    - "w3bs1te"
    - "h4ndsh4k3"
	
First team to get the correct string in reply to the
 email wins.
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 
 HINT: Serving Order... 103,206,097,274</file>
  
  <customthemefile path="sys" name="Cyan_Tech.sys" themePath="Themes/CyanTech.xml" />
  <customthemefile path="sys" name="Bubbles.sys" themePath="Themes/Bubbles.xml" />
  <customthemefile path="sys" name="Special_HackerJam.sys" themePath="Themes/HackerJam_HW.xml" />
  
  <dlink target="ctfMain03" />
  <dlink target="ctfMain04" />
  <dlink target="playerComp" />
  <dlink target="ctfMain02" />
</Computer>